<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="gsw_content_information">
    <gsw_content_information action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <article><![CDATA[<p><strong><span style="color: #dd9122;">Required</span></strong></p>
<p>To enable the chat window, you&#39;ll need to configure the Service Portal Web Client for portals such as Service Portal (SP), Employee Service Center (ESC) or Customer Service Portal (CSP). </p>
<p>To create a Service Portal Agent Chat Configuration, click the &#39;New&#39; button from the Service Portal Agent Chat Configurations list view. Mark the record as active, fill in the name and select an order number. You can select the portals where you want the widget to show.</p>]]></article>
        <best_practice_acceptable>false</best_practice_acceptable>
        <dependent_on_contents/>
        <dependent_on_plugins/>
        <dependent_on_plugins_ids/>
        <description/>
        <embedded_help_qualifier/>
        <end_point>/sp_agent_chat_config_list.do</end_point>
        <end_point_open_mode>2</end_point_open_mode>
        <end_point_type>1</end_point_type>
        <field/>
        <filter/>
        <filter_result/>
        <implicit_dependent_on/>
        <implicit_plugin_dependencies/>
        <is_dynamic>false</is_dynamic>
        <more_info_available>false</more_info_available>
        <more_info_html><![CDATA[<p>To prepare for configuration, gather or prepare the following items:</p>
<ul style="list-style-position: inside;"><li>Company logos for your chat windows and if using Virtual Agent, the avatars for your virtual agent bots. If chat is run in its own browser window, a thumbnail of the branding logo displays automatically in the browser tab. The images must be in .jpg, .png, .bmp, .gif, .jpeg, .ico, or .svg file format. The images can be high resolution, but the image display is scaled based on the aspect ratio.</li><li>Custom menu icons for the chat menu (formerly called the Contact support menu), if you want to change the icons for the default menu items or add icons for new menu items. The icons must be in .svg file format. For better resolution, use a single-color icon.</li><li>The color names or RGB color numbers for your configuration. You can specify the colors for UI items such as font colors and background colors for chat bubbles, buttons, and notifications displayed.</li><li>Contact information for your support organization, such as support call hours, call center support phone number, and support email address. You can customize the information in the support menu by adding or changing menu items, including the text and icons displayed. You can also control the visibility of the menu items (show or hide menu options).</li></ul>]]></more_info_html>
        <order>1</order>
        <parent display_value="">efd5908fdb0adc10ab1354e4dc961957</parent>
        <parents>efd5908fdb0adc10ab1354e4dc961957,f40027b2dbc6dc10ab1354e4dc96194b</parents>
        <plugin_id/>
        <property_name/>
        <property_value/>
        <quick_startable>false</quick_startable>
        <root_parent display_value="">f40027b2dbc6dc10ab1354e4dc96194b</root_parent>
        <skippable>true</skippable>
        <supports_child_content>false</supports_child_content>
        <sys_class_name>gsw_content_information</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>qianyi.xu@snc</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2020-07-21 19:40:56</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>c821485bdb021050ab1354e4dc961970</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>36</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Service Portal Web Client*</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="WS1UEMSpoke" source="x_646971_uemconn_0">860d52f507d430105740f96d7c1ed0b1</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="WS1UEMSpoke">860d52f507d430105740f96d7c1ed0b1</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>gsw_content_information_c821485bdb021050ab1354e4dc961970</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>samantha.santo@snc</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2020-10-12 21:11:54</sys_updated_on>
        <table/>
        <title>Service Portal Web Client*</title>
        <weight>1</weight>
    </gsw_content_information>
    <sys_translated_text action="delete_multiple" query="documentkey=c821485bdb021050ab1354e4dc961970"/>
</record_update>
